yo guys what's up dude a late night late
night mapping Scobie it's kind of cool
so the first thing that I want to talk
about gonna flip you guys the other way
so we released a driver monitor and
challenge today to come AI yeah I know I
heard this so should we cancel Ford is
it not the year of the for it anymore
the car would cancel Ford don't buy Ford
guys but yeah so the kind I travel
monitor challenge but I'm not going to
tease you I did promise mapping so I'm
gonna show you what I've been working on
today it's called depth net point cloud
we have a really low quality depth net
that I trained in GTA our machine
learning team over here has been working
hard and it's hopefully gonna get me a
better death nut this is what we have I
move you over to this monitor look at
that when I talk about the precision of
our HD max so I'm generating this little
mapping area right now this is from 100
frames and the craziest thing is I can
zoom out and that's a 3G that's a little
piece of 3d world that's been generated
now there's nothing special about this
route so I asked on slack for energy to
send me another route unfortunately it
does take an absurdly long time so
you'll have to bear with me on it but
yeah that is fully three-dimensional I
can see that building over there you can
see the point clouds that have been
generated here yeah and that is with a
really low quality depth cam
well we've been working really hard on
is our master riser so we're recovering
precise locations of everything using
the gray pandas so I'm going to close
this one out here and I'm gonna copy and
paste energies around now I think it's a
night time route which we've never
actually tested before it so I have no
idea if this is gonna work and it takes
about ten minutes so we'll try to find
something to do
that's all do party okay here we go so
yeah
this runs part of our pipeline it has to
do all the processing and yeah I love
the super hearts by the way guys let's
talk about the monitoring challenge for
a bet so what we're trying to do is
you're trying to track people's faces
and you're trying to track their
eyeballs and see where they're looking
so you can see let's see who's
distracted in this photo so you can see
Vivian's looking off to the that way
there it's kind of hard to tell with
Eddie you know he's got the sunglasses
on I did all of the super hearts Carlos
looks like he's paying attention but so
I can so you can check that out on
github so that route over there is still
processing it takes a while yeah so in
order to track through sunglasses you're
gonna need some infrared stuff but we
can take a look at these videos here oh
yeah I should probably disable this wait
this is your route you just sit in
traffic well this is gonna do you energy
you're just sitting traffic wait minute
500 do you actually mean 500 I don't
think you mean 500 I tried minute 8 but
this is just sitting in traffic I'm
sitting in traffic yeah okay you're
doing it starting to move maybe we'll
try the next minute maybe the next
minute I'll have less traffic yeah so
these are the videos from the the driver
monitoring um I can show you another one
that I have prepared it's not as good
let's see what this one's gonna do
so a lot of the quality issues here are
because I've got the notes bad but our
mesh risers pretty good so let's see if
we can make a tiny little chunk of 3d
map out of this let's see what we can
kind of see what happened and what
messed up there and we zoom out
it's zoom out so you see that I'm in a
canyon yeah it looks like the depth not
really just messed up there but it looks
much better yeah
so we're building 3d maps of the world
now if you have a go over Greg Hannah
and you're earning gold star routes I
think we're gonna make these maps
available to you we can look around in
here and see that's actually pretty good
she goes grass off to the side here you
see the trees here you see the trees
over here yeah pretty cool so yeah and
Archie was just sitting in traffic and
yes we want to sit in traffic guys but
um so no we're not displaying gold stars
yet uh hang on let me just set oh mmm
threads equals one the right it's slow
let's see okay this is better look we're
not sitting in traffic anymore that's
pretty cool oh that's gonna work well if
that actually works I don't know why
your times are so labeled wrong though
if we're doing all this matching we're
finding all these features it's pretty
cool
I said well just let that run for a
while yeah what's up about Scheffer plus
why don't we work so late cuz you want
to win then it was the stayed up late
the Toyota Research Institute they don't
wanna win I've heard from the other guys
told me like cool what's your opinion on
bootcamps of data science look you're
not alone
here's the thing about a boot camp right
if someone told you that you could learn
Chinese in eight weeks
would you believe them oh no right yep
someone tells you you can learn data
science or Python or programming I don't
know why you believe them right I did
shave the beard it grew back
I shaved I shaved that Friday throwing
out that night
if you move your GPS antenna should you
recalibrate oh by the way so you can see
the routes processing here we're just
you know generating all the features on
here and getting the matches oh no you
don't need to recalibrate after you
remove your GPS antenna how long for the
driver attention software is open source
as soon as you write it I'm very
disappointed by Ford's announcement I
knew Ford would let me down a new Ford
had let me down gross alright so we're
gonna see energy we're gonna see if your
route works oh this is taking forever so
slow look at that guy pushing that
carriage across the road with those slow
feature back there
that's brutal oh that's brutally slow
guys what's the use of the depth map so
once we make it good no it's not
obviously we get rid of warps I mean
Harold wrote Harold slam it's better
Harold you want until the scope is about
Harold slam you want telescope is about
Harold slam no they asked if we were
using web slam and I said no yeah yo
guys it doesn't just use cameras it uses
grape handed GPS is it uses I am use we
got full sensor fusion is crazy oh yeah
this thing
[Music]
you're moving through space and all the
blue things are things your camera seen
through gold things are the GPS
satellites the red ball is where you
chased me cuz everyone's chasing the
ball yeah yeah we think you know Ford
canceled all their cars yeah so
downstairs we're running mess 3d
everyone's very sad how slow it is I
didn't pull all right good I won't pull
comments competing with space legs no
and I'm competing this face likes and
the Rockets aren't they keeping fusion
no I heard it's just f-150s
of police interceptors and the folk is
active which hasn't been introduced yet
no I really think that's why Ford did it
because they hate us ah look at that
that's taking way too long it's not even
running nice did you yeah oh no scope
ease
it's so slow it's so slow what are you
gonna do we gotta kill ten minutes not a
columnstore no speed what what car do
you have
oh you have a weird car let's go good
car yes a CRV photos like exactly Ford
got rid of the cars it's a
scorched-earth policy I love that you
know that's what I would do if I run a
company one will shiver plus EGR we
really never shipped to really chef
released
HDR which I love you guys I'll let you
in on a secret
if you run an open pilot with passive
equals one it's the same thing as ship
replies yes Tillie the session reunified
it um so energy error running mesh 3d no
speed I can try to hack Messer eg if you
give me a second
no speed oh no oh it's not even using
speed oh this is stupid okay
it doesn't even use speed don't worry
guys I hacked it now kierra speed T and
sure sorted use it for no rod okay we'll
get rid of the no rod observations they
really need them all right so we got a
download some from NASA you guys
know where the satellites are don't
worry NASA doesn't know where everything
is this doesn't run this is a tragedy
and we're gonna just quit this mapping
scope being disgrace it's downloading
some stuff whoo hourly will that's
exciting
Harold you don't use speed but if cars
don't have speed it doesn't work yeah no
yeah now it's working like I got you
blocks GPS ten that means you've got a
great panel no we're good we're good
we're good
I fixed it no don't worry your car
doesn't have speed because it's a weird
Civic right like you have some weird
here you go CRV you're not supported in
the back end oh we should do that unify
with on pal oh oh so the full courser
panda you mean yeah okay cool I'm so
energy I think when you get your stuff
up streamed it'll work because we use we
use the car library right okay cool yeah
we got us chickens gonna work
alright guys so mr. D's running down
don't worry I hacked it for now we have
five minutes left and it's running so
let's download that video so we can take
a look and I'll see what its gonna look
like so let's go in here and you've been
uploading oh you've been uploading d
cameras to me thank you thank you for
your d cameras
d cameras or driver cameras some most
happy when we get those anymore why do
you Road videos no okay so this is what
we'll be napping right here oh look at
them gold marches man for the depth not
understands golden arches so the depth
note wasn't trained on videos that look
anything like this we have a new depth
net coming out and I will show you guys
so I want you to remember how bad this
way so you can see I'm good the next one
I so unfortunately now it's taking even
longer it's decided it wants to be slow
which is lame
this is good footage right yo the HDR is
so good no you can't get a 99 Wrangler
to dry itself and if you ask again
that's a bad question
I'll penny from the periscope I know
it's late but we still got the banhammer
don't worry how old is the depth net
from last year that was a bot all right
so I'm arguing with BOTS let's see what
we're at here we go that's how much we
have left so you guys can like do the
countdown up Network to eight minutes
great high quality should you sell your
Ford yeah probably
I don't think no no maybe I'll ship
something the main reason we got a
fusion is because data speeds using it
and we were disappointed yeah she's nice
car talk about the challenge for eight
minutes okay that sounds good so let's
take a look at these videos and think
about what we wanted to do videos this
okay so here's Vivian's video so you can
see your face here you want to track the
position of her face so a face you can
think of this like I it has pitch and
yaw and then once you have the face you
can track the eye position as well so
you probably want to get these corners
and then figure out the rotation of the
eyeball
then you can project a ray out of the
eye
and you can figure out where the driver
is looking doesn't that sound like
useful data to train a self-driving car
yep I was always thinking you know um so
download our challenge go to komete I
get up and you'll see that it's linked
it's one of the hope I can't show you
that that's the private data they've
been recorded with me on videos right
here on shopback oh I got AI it's taking
even more time that's a route with a lot
of stuff um so we're hiring a full-time
driver monitoring engineer come join us
at SF to work with these videos if you
guys didn't see our medium post about
safety and driver attention I would
definitely check that out
look this guy made an open-source
allegedly thingy but it said will be out
soon so it's not yeah I want to do a
little bit more than just glam
classification with a neural network
aren't you want to extract some vectors
about the face um usually transaction to
classify the drivers looking yeah I
don't just want to classify the drivers
looking I want to get like a
multi-dimensional vector
I want to effectively like represent
people with like cartoon heads right and
if you could overlay like a nice cartoon
head in a person with big like anime
eyes you know do I think over stays in
the driverless car industry yes yeah
yeah I don't know seems like I don't
just want to do glanced classification I
want to do more than that
yeah I like like anime eyes let's Google
anime eyes and still read yeah no no
there with big eyes yeah yeah I want
like like anime eyes like this you know
like big eyes that are really very
visible where someone's looking I could
not get a rule 34 it here um oh we're
not in the home were in the office is
glare Caucasian better just a six minute
timer absolutely lot can happen in six
minutes
what value do you see in doing more Oh
more than just glance classification
well so here's the thing right it's
optional for people to upload their uh
their video to us because you know you
don't wanna take everyone's video from
the front-facing camera wow this is
taking even more time Harold mr. et is
so spoiled 22 me too it's per second
how about waking sleepy drivers yeah
that kind of stuff - you know how open
people's eyes are that could all be
important stuff know what and what do we
do Freddie here
thank you sunglasses we could track is
the track is oh yeah guys go to our
github submit that challenge do well on
the challenge and we'll bring you out
here for a micro internship ok so I got
over you right I got ours what I'm doing
tomorrow me right in the Kalman filter
and say we're not gonna like it's if you
take your eyes off the road for two
seconds it's ok 10 seconds less ok I
really just got this probably isn't even
gonna be that cool we're probably gonna
wait and it's not gonna be that cool
it's taking for ever bros
nope let's see let's see what our
notifications are on Twitter
I'm checking Twitter let's copy that we
shouldn't be doing all right what else
can we show you while we wait nothing
all we can do is wait it's terrible
terrible I do why I got a bot just
repeat your message I don't know man I
don't know why there's boxing yeah I
understand what periscope can't clean
their house up is this worth waiting 12
minutes oh yeah okay you want to go
check out the GPU farm right I'll go
check out the GPU I know where we're
going
what's the next development least
tomorrow no actually have something cool
in the GPU far we've been expanding the
printers look at them look at our 3d
printer are me when I go to my bedroom
nice but look at this printer are me
yeah so these are the GPUs over here
these are the storage machines over here
they're multiple I do the 3d printer
armies getting uh getting really huge
look you can see some great Panda
stuffing
and looking to get finished printing
Jesus crap who pays your power well we
pack let's see these ones finished
reading all of those look like quality
those look like quality gray panda
pieces right here or electricity bills
crazy high lights we're going we don't
need lights pistachio why don't you have
your light on
let's say settings light turn lights on
in sleep mode absolutely love lights
ping DJ you need some lights in sleep
mode to enable sleep mode that turn
lights on and sleep mode power is cheap
guys light turn lights on in sleep mode
yo having a lot of something is a whole
lot of fun so I'm gonna have dim lights
the Valerie's like two old dim over
there oh these are some great Panda
pieces some great panda backs
oh great pandas off of like a nut left
it let's say this is trash what do some
of these are good you just that one
there is bad so we go through them the
QA everything we assemble them know
what's up this one need some whites
yeah I saw this crazy expensive power
it's like progressive taxation on the
power system furs are pretty anything
right now
Eddie's sick
all right let's see if we're finished oh
well we have a male person their home
right now check out our new fulfillment
center
this is rolling your star chips from you
see this this is the last 128 gig Eon in
existence so I don't know if someone
maybe already bought it but when that
one sells we're out of stock guys were
running low on us you're running low on
eels
we could've bother you on to that it's
not even close to done no it's not even
close to done so let's go peace you guys
don't get to see anymore Maps mapping
scope he was a scam
tell your friends come AI as a scam no
go to shop that comedy I think sure to
buy stuff plenty of midnight black
laughs to the new hardware platform ooh
where'd you hear about that all right
that's it we don't get to see anymore
maps maybe I'll post a screenshot once
we're good and slack but mesially these
too slow we got to make much to do
faster
all right ladies go peace